var allQuestions = [{
    question: "Which part of speech names a person, place, or thing?",
    option1: "noun",
    option2: "adjective",
    option3: "preposition",
    option4: "verb",
    answer: 1
  }, {
    question: "Which part of speech replaces a noun?",
    option1: "conjunction",
    option2: "adverb",
    option3: "pronoun",
    option4: "preposition",
    answer: 3
  }, {
    question: " Which part of speech describes a noun or a pronoun?",
    option1: "adjective",
    option2: "adverb",
    option3: "conjunction",
    option4: "verb",
    answer: 1
  },{
    question: "Which part of speech modifies a verb, adjective, or adverb?",
    option1: "preposition",
    option2: " verb",
    option3: "noun",
    option4: "adverb",
    answer: 4
  },{
    question: "Define:  Verb",
    option1: "An action",
    option2: "A word that gives more detail about nouns",
    option3: "A person, place, thing, or idea",
    option4: "A word that gives more details about verbs",
    answer: 1
  },{
    question: "Define:  Noun",
    option1: "An action",
    option2: "A word that gives more detail about nouns",
    option3: "A person, place, thing, or idea",
    option4: "A word that gives more details about verbs",
    answer: 3
  },{
    question: "Define:  Adverb",
    option1: "An action",
    option2: "A word that gives more detail about nouns",
    option3: "A person, place, thing, or idea",
    option4: "A word that modifies another adverb, adjective, or verb ",
    answer: 4
  },{
    question: "Tylar's hair is silky brown. Which word is the Adjective? ",
    option1: "Tylar's",
    option2: "Hair",
    option3: "Silky",
    option4: "All of the Above",
    answer: 3
  },{
    question: "Elizabeth climbed the tree really fast. Which word is the verb?",
    option1: "Elizabeth",
    option2: "Climbed",
    option3: "Really",
    option4: "Fast",
    answer: 2
  },{
    question: "  Jill jumped on top of her bed with joy!  How many prepositions are in this sentence?",
    option1: "1",
    option2: "3",
    option3: "5",
    option4: "2",
    answer: 2
}];